http://www.campfarley.com/privacy-statement

Camp FarleyCOVID 19 UPDATELetter from our DirectorRates and DatesGeneral InformationPrograms and ActivitiesOvernight CampParent GuideDay CampHorseback RidingLIT ProgramAbout Camp FarleyCamp StaffCamp PhotosSummer EmploymentOff Season RentalsCampership InformationCampership ApplicationPrivacy StatementCamper EmailContact Us
Privacy Statement
Camp Farley collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Camp Farley also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Camp Farley. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Website addresses. This information is used by Camp Farley for the operation of the services, to maintain quality of the services, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Camp Farley Website.
Camp Farley will use your information to mail or email you promotional materials pertaining to our summer camp program. If you provide us with personal information as a potential staff member, your information may be used in carrying out our reference and background checks as part of our staff hiring process. If you register for summer camp online, the information will be used to register a child for summer camp and collect payment information to be used to pay for the child's registration. Email addresses provided on the registration form will be used to communicate information about summer camp and keep you connected with Camp Farley during the other three seasons. No information you provide us will be passed on to any advertisers or third parties outside Camp Farley.
For children under the age of 13: In compliance with the Child Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) you must ask your parents to give your personal information online.
If you do not wish to receive any further mailings from Camp Farley or would like to be removed from our current mail list, please contact us.
